CONNOR BEST

SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER

INFO

PHONE

3219001989

EMAIL

connorwbest95@gmail.com

LINKS

LinkedIn

<u>Portfolio</u>

<u>Github</u>

SKILLS

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

React.js

Wordpress

UX/UI Design

Figma

Node.js

PHP

MySQL

Google Cloud Platform

PROFILE

Full Stack Web Developer and marketing graduate working to build first-rate user experiences. Comfortable in agile environments that require high levels of communication with leadership and clients to meet both quality expectations and deadlines. Proven efficiency in Wordpress Theme development and ecommerce.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Senior Web Developer, Feeding Children Everywhere

Longwood, FL

Nov 2018 — Present

- Built a new order management process by adding both shipping and inventory management in addition to improving the checkout process and reducing php worker limits by over 50%.
- Completed a full redesign of our wordpress theme that included dynamic content sections to take full advantage of Wordpress as a CMS.
- Developed custom Wordpress & Woocommerce functionality with php to allow for user customization of orders.
- Reduced server resource usage by over 60% to allow for faster page loads and a better user experience.

Customer Service Representative, Neulion Inc.

Sanford, FL

Feb 2015 — Nov 2018

- Use CRM's such as Kayako and ZenDesk to communicate with customers regarding billing or technical issues for organizations such as the UFC, NFL and BTN.
- Provide technical support to customers on platforms such as ios, android and web through a live chat service, Snap Engage.

Digital Marketing Intern, Neulion Inc.

Sanford, FL

May 2018 — Jul 2018

- Wrote and edited multiple newsletters and informational documents such as 'How to Grow and Engage an Audience on Social Media" which resulted in recognition from corporate partners.
- Analyzed web traffic and created reports based on Google Analytics data from our college partners to determine the cause of subscriber drop off.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Business Administration, Marketing, University of Central Florida

Orlando, FL

Jan 2016 — Dec 2018

Technical Certificate of Completion, University of Central Florida Coding Bootcamp

Orlando, FL

Jun 2018 — Dec 2018